Traslate by Kisskh.live Provide [ Admin Qari]
الترجمة بواسطة Kisskh.live توفير [المسؤول قاري]
(See Your Love)
(انظر حبك)
(Episode 11)
(الحلقة 11)
(Luckily, it is not too late)
(لحسن الحظ، لم يفت الأوان بعد)
(I didn't lose it; I can still have it)
(لم أفقدها؛ لا يزال بإمكاني الحصول عليها)
Zixiang, ask Shaopeng to come out for fruit.
زيكسيانج، اطلب من شاوبينج أن يخرج للحصول على الفاكهة.
Zixiang?
زيكسيانج؟
Coming. Got it.
قادم. حصلت عليه.
Ms. Zheng, why did you ask me out privately?
السيدة تشنغ، لماذا طلبت مني الخروج معك على انفراد؟
What would you like to drink?
ماذا تحب أن تشرب؟
I don't think we're close enough to drink coffee together.
لا أعتقد أننا قريبين بما يكفي لشرب القهوة معًا.
When I first went to Hongcheng for a meeting,
عندما ذهبت لأول مرة إلى هونغتشنغ لحضور اجتماع،
I saw you being jealous because of a pen.
رأيتك تغار بسبب قلم.
(Jiang Shaopeng)
(جيانغ شاوبنغ)
Shaopeng's pen.
قلم شاوبنج.
It's mine.
إنها لي.
Through supervision,
من خلال الإشراف،
I can see many things.
أستطيع أن أرى أشياء كثيرة.
Your reaction that day was very interesting.
رد فعلك في ذلك اليوم كان مثيرا للاهتمام للغاية.
So I asked someone to investigate
لذلك طلبت من شخص ما التحقيق
your relationship with Jiang Shaopeng.
علاقتك مع جيانغ شاو بينغ.
You two are a couple?
هل أنتم زوجين؟
No.
لا.
One-sided love doesn't count.
الحب من طرف واحد لا يهم.
You have a crush on him?
هل أنت معجبة به؟
If it's not about work, I should get going.
إذا لم يكن الأمر يتعلق بالعمل، يجب أن أذهب.
Collaborate with me to get our own man back.
تعاون معي لاستعادة رجلنا.
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
(Fenghong Mall Bid-Winning Celebration Party)
(حفلة الاحتفال بالفوز بالمزايدة في مركز فينجهونج التجاري)
Getting the land is just the beginning.
الحصول على الأرض هو مجرد البداية. (حفل الاحتفال بفوز مركز التسوق Fenghong Mall بالمزايدة)
Everyone, please continue to work hard
الجميع، من فضلكم استمروا في العمل الجاد
so that I can have more chances to slack off.
حتى أتمكن من الحصول على المزيد من الفرص للتراخي.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
No need to save money for your boss.
لا داعي لتوفير المال لرئيسك.
Everyone, the bonus will be transferred to your account along with next month's salary.
الجميع، سيتم تحويل المكافأة إلى حسابك مع راتب الشهر المقبل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you, Boss.
شكرا لك يا رئيس.
Why did you invite me to your celebration party?
لماذا دعوتني إلى حفلتك الاحتفالية؟
You can have a free meal.
يمكنك الحصول على وجبة مجانية.
Isn't it good to save money for you?
أليس من الجيد توفير المال بالنسبة لك؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Thanks, bro.
شكرا لك أخي.
Well...
حسنًا...
can I pack some?
هل يمكنني أن أحزم بعضًا منها؟
Whatever.
أيا كان.
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
I'll pack some for you as midnight snacks later.
سأحضر لك بعضًا منها كوجبة خفيفة في منتصف الليل لاحقًا.
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
Congratulations on winning the bid.
مبروك الفوز بالمناقصة.
So, do you want to buy my saltern?
إذن، هل تريد شراء الملح الخاص بي؟
Thank you, Mr. Huang.
شكرا لك السيد هوانغ.
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
Okay. We'll talk later.
حسنًا، سنتحدث لاحقًا.
Mr. Huang, this way please.
السيد هوانغ، من هذا الطريق من فضلك.
Didn't you say you invited Jiang Shaopeng here?
ألم تقل أنك دعوت جيانغ شاو بينغ إلى هنا؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
He said the elderly person he takes care of encountered an emergency situation.
وقال إن الشخص المسن الذي يعتني به واجه حالة طارئة.
He already set off. He'll be here later.
لقد انطلق بالفعل، وسوف يكون هنا لاحقًا.
Boss.
رئيس.
Cousin!
ابن عم!
Cousin, long time no see.
ابن العم، لم نلتقي منذ وقت طويل.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Your shoelaces.
أربطة حذائك.
Cousin, let me do it.
ابن عمي، دعني أفعل ذلك.
Who is he?
من هو؟
He treats Yang Zixiang quite well.
يعامل يانغ زيكسيانج بشكل جيد للغاية.
Jiang Shaopeng's rival in love?
منافس جيانغ شاو بينغ في الحب؟
It would be troublesome if he is.
سيكون الأمر مزعجًا إذا كان كذلك.
Now this is more troublesome.
الآن هذا الأمر أكثر إزعاجا.
You and Yang Zixiang are from two different worlds.
أنت ويانغ زيكسيانج من عالمين مختلفين.
You didn't keep your promise.
لم تفي بوعدك.
You don't deserve Zixiang.
أنت لا تستحق Zixiang.
His world is dazzling.
عالمه مبهر.
Yours is ordinary
خاصتك عادية
and very quiet.
وهادئة للغاية.
Give up.
يستسلم.
He'll go back to America and marry me soon.
سيعود إلى أمريكا ويتزوجني قريبًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You can't help him with his family, career, or life.
لا يمكنك مساعدته في شؤون عائلته، أو مهنته، أو حياته.
How long do you think you can stay with him like this?
إلى متى تعتقدين أنك تستطيعين البقاء معه بهذه الطريقة؟
Cousin.
ابن عم.
Jiang Shaopeng, slow down.
جيانغ شاوبنغ، أبطئ.
Why are you angry?
لماذا انت غاضب؟
I'm not angry.
أنا لست غاضبا.
You are.
أنت.
I'm not.
انا لا.
I...
أنا...
Who is the man who helped you tie your shoelaces?
من هو الرجل الذي ساعدك في ربط حذائك؟
My cousin.
ابن عمي.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Your cousin?
ابن عمك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
You're jealous.
أنت غيور.
I'll forgive you if you admit it.
سأسامحك إذا اعترفت بذلك.
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
You're jealous.
أنت غيور.
Jiang Shaopeng...
جيانغ شاوبنغ ...
Do you want to have a drink to celebrate?
هل تريد أن تشرب مشروبًا للاحتفال؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Do you think by doing this,
هل تعتقد أنه بالقيام بهذا،
you can change their feelings for each other?
هل يمكنك تغيير مشاعرهم تجاه بعضهم البعض؟
Shaopeng won't just give up because of what you did.
لن يستسلم شاوبنج بسبب ما فعلته.
Why don't you think of a way?
لماذا لا تفكر في طريقة؟
Get pregnant?
الحمل؟
What kind of way is that?
ما هذا النوع من الطرق؟
Learned it from palace intrigue dramas?
هل تعلمت ذلك من دراما المؤامرات القصرية؟
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
Miss, are you kidding me?
آنستي هل أنت تمزحين معي؟
I have no other way.
ليس لدي طريقة أخرى.
I've never been in a relationship.
لم أكن في علاقة أبدًا.
It's all because Zixiang wants to ruin the plan and break off the engagement.
كل هذا لأن زيكسيانج يريد إفساد الخطة وقطع الخطوبة.
Otherwise, I wouldn't need to be so worried.
وإلا فلن أحتاج إلى القلق إلى هذا الحد.
So...
لذا...
you don't like Yang Zixiang.
أنت لا تحب يانغ Zixiang.
Do I have to?
هل يجب علي ذلك؟
Wait.
انتظر.
I drank alcohol.
لقد شربت الكحول.
I stink.
أنا كريهة الرائحة.
I want to take a shower first.
أريد أن أستحم أولاً.
Wait.
انتظر.
Let me take a shower first.
دعني أستحم أولاً.
I stink.
أنا كريهة الرائحة.
Wait, Jiang Shaopeng!
انتظر، جيانغ شاوبنغ!
I said I want to take a shower.
قلت أريد أن أستحم.
I didn't say we should take a shower!
لم أقل أننا يجب أن نستحم!
♫Saying I love you♫
♫أقول أحبك♫
♫Even my fingers are wildly saying I love you♫
♫حتى أصابعي تقول بجنون "أحبك"♫
♫I can't hear you, just foolishly waiting in place♫
♫لا أستطيع سماعك، فقط أنتظر في مكاني بغباء♫
♫Longing to open your heart♫
♫أشتاق إلى فتح قلبك♫
♫I want to scream stop and give up♫
♫أريد أن أصرخ توقف واستسلم♫
♫Trying to forget how hard we've tried♫
♫أحاول أن أنسى مدى الجهد الذي بذلناه♫
♫I can't forget the promise made that day♫
♫لا أستطيع أن أنسى الوعد الذي قطعته في ذلك اليوم♫
♫Closing my eyes, all I hear is your voice♫
♫أغمض عيني، كل ما أسمعه هو صوتك♫
♫Saying I love you♫
♫أقول أحبك♫
♫Even my words are wildly saying I love you♫
♫حتى كلماتي تقول بجنون "أحبك"♫
♫I can't hear you, just foolishly waiting in place♫
♫لا أستطيع سماعك، فقط أنتظر في مكاني بغباء♫
♫Two hearts are so close♫
♫قلبان قريبان جدًا♫
♫I want to scream stop and give up♫
♫أريد أن أصرخ توقف واستسلم♫
♫Trying to forget how deeply it hurts♫
♫أحاول أن أنسى مدى الألم العميق♫
♫I can't get rid of it♫
♫لا أستطيع التخلص منه♫
♫The expression of having been loved♫
♫التعبير عن الحب♫
♫Closing my eyes, all I hear is your voice♫
♫أغمض عيني، كل ما أسمعه هو صوتك♫
Wang Xinjia.
وانغ شينجيا.
Don't disturb them.
لا تزعجهم.
They...
هم...
Why hasn't Yang Zixiang come out for breakfast?
لماذا لم يخرج يانغ زيكسيانج لتناول الإفطار؟
You care so much about my little boss.
أنت تهتم كثيرًا بمديري الصغير.
You like him?
هل يعجبك؟
Yang Zixiang saved me
أنقذني يانغ Zixiang
and let me stay in his house.
ودعني أبقى في بيته.
I'm indebted to him.
أنا مدين له.
Of course I care about him.
بالطبع أنا أهتم به.
You're so grateful?
هل أنت ممتن جدًا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
It's my basic principle.
إنه مبدأي الأساسي.
You don't need to work today, right?
لا تحتاج إلى العمل اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
I don't. What?
انا لا افعل ماذا؟
I've been very busy lately.
لقد كنت مشغولاً جداً في الآونة الأخيرة.
Help me.
ساعدني.
200 NT dollars per hour.
200 دولار تايواني في الساعة.
No problem. Let me finish my breakfast first.
لا مشكلة، دعني أنهي إفطاري أولاً.
Thank you, Cheng Fengjie.
شكرا لك، تشنغ فنغ جيه.
What's my task?
ما هي مهمتي؟
Being my secretary.
أن تكون سكرتيرتي.
Secretary?
سكرتيرة؟
Let me make it clear first. My English isn't very good.
دعني أوضح الأمر أولاً: لغتي الإنجليزية ليست جيدة جدًا.
I type very slowly.
أكتب ببطء شديد.
And I don't know how to use a computer at all.
وأنا لا أعرف كيفية استخدام الكمبيوتر على الإطلاق.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I want you to do it because it suits you.
أريدك أن تفعل ذلك لأنه يناسبك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
He asked me to be his secretary,
لقد طلب مني أن أكون سكرتيرته،
but I'm doing manual labor.
لكنني أقوم بعمل يدوي.
His smile is so insincere.
ابتسامته غير صادقة
What does it feel like to have
ما هو شعورك عندما تمتلك
such a popular boss?
مثل هذا الرئيس الشعبي؟
He's an elite coming back from America.
إنه أحد النخبة العائدة من أمريكا.
He's handsome and has a good personality.
إنه وسيم ولديه شخصية جيدة.
Good personality?
شخصية جيدة؟
His personality is terrible.
شخصيته فظيعة.
Hey.
يا.
Your perseverance is a thousand times better than your killing skills, isn't it?
إن مثابرتك أفضل ألف مرة من مهاراتك في القتل، أليس كذلك؟
He's very scheming.
إنه ماكر للغاية.
And he's a playboy.
وهو رجل لعوب.
Handsome guy.
رجل وسيم.
How about a drink with us?
ماذا عن تناول مشروب معنا؟
Apart from his handsome appearance, there's
بصرف النظر عن مظهره الوسيم، هناك
nothing else that makes him popular.
لا يوجد شيء آخر يجعله مشهورًا.
Special Assistant Cheng is that kind of person?
المساعد الخاص تشنغ هو هذا النوع من الأشخاص؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Wang Xinjia.
وانغ شينجيا.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Black tea
الشاي الأسود
with three slices of lemon,
مع ثلاث شرائح من الليمون،
no sugar.
بدون سكر.
Okay.
تمام.
Three slices of lemon.
ثلاث شرائح من الليمون.
Are you pregnant?
هل انت حامل؟
It'd be yours.
ستكون لك.
I have excellent hearing.
لدي سمع ممتاز.
Wang Xinjia!
وانغ شينجيا!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Mom, stop trying to find me another boyfriend.
أمي، توقفي عن محاولة العثور على صديق آخر لي.
I will marry Yang Zixiang. I promise.
سأتزوج يانغ زيكسيانغ. أعدك بذلك.
Your smartphone is innocent.
هاتفك الذكي بريء.
Taking your anger out on it won't do you any good, right?
إن إخراج غضبك لن يفيدك بأي شيء، أليس كذلك؟
I have plenty of money to buy a new one.
لدي الكثير من المال لشراء واحدة جديدة.
Is it your money or your family's money?
هل هذه أموالك أم أموال عائلتك؟
It's on me.
إنه عليّ.
I hardly eat carbohydrates.
أنا نادرا ما آكل الكربوهيدرات.
You're worried you'd gain weight?
هل أنت قلق من أنك ستكتسب وزنا؟
Who's worried?
من القلق؟
All my meals are designed by a nutritionist.
يتم تصميم جميع وجباتي من قبل أخصائي التغذية.
So obedient?
مطيع جدًا؟
You even have a nutritionist for that?
هل لديك خبير تغذية لذلك؟
You...
أنت...
are quite cute.
لطيفين جدًا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I heard what you just said on the phone.
لقد سمعت ما قلته للتو على الهاتف.
If you can't marry Yang Zixiang,
إذا لم تتمكن من الزواج من يانغ زيشيانغ،
your mother will find another man for you?
هل ستجد والدتك رجلاً آخر لك؟
If I want to enjoy the wealth of my family,
إذا أردت أن أستمتع بثروة عائلتي،
I have to take on the responsibilities that come with it.
يتوجب علي أن أتحمل المسؤوليات التي تأتي معها.
Marriage is just another form of contract.
الزواج هو مجرد شكل آخر من أشكال العقد.
Would you develop feelings for someone
هل لديك مشاعر تجاه شخص ما؟
you signed a contract with?
لقد وقعت عقدا مع؟
But marriage is built on love.
لكن الزواج مبني على الحب.
Why do people sign work contracts?
لماذا يوقع الناس عقود العمل؟
Sign work contracts?
توقيع عقود العمل؟
To ensure mutual rights and obligations
لضمان الحقوق والالتزامات المتبادلة
to avoid unfair treatment or unnecessary losses.
لتجنب المعاملة غير العادلة أو الخسائر غير الضرورية.
You have a point.
لديك نقطة.
So Yang Zixiang is a jerk.
لذا فإن Yang Zixiang أحمق.
Why are you suddenly jumping to that conclusion?
لماذا تتوصل فجأة إلى هذا الاستنتاج؟
Why did he fall in love with someone?
لماذا وقع في حب شخص ما؟
He even displayed his affection in front of me.
حتى أنه أظهر عاطفته أمامي.
He's a scumbag publicly having an affair.
إنه شخص حقير لديه علاقة علنية.
I won't let him get away with it.
لن أسمح له بالهرب من ذلك.
When you truly fall in love with someone, you'll understand.
عندما تقع في حب شخص ما حقًا، سوف تفهم ذلك.
Love isn't something you can control.
الحب ليس شيئا يمكنك التحكم به.
And marriage isn't just a contract.
والزواج ليس مجرد عقد.
It's also a promise that you'll love someone forever.
إنه أيضًا وعد بأنك ستحب شخصًا إلى الأبد.
You've watched too many idol dramas, haven't you?
لقد شاهدت الكثير من الدراما الأيدولزية، أليس كذلك؟
We agreed to work together to break them up.
اتفقنا على العمل معًا لفض هذه الخلافات.
Don't forget that.
لا تنسى ذلك .
Okay.
تمام.
Is he the reason why you broke your promise?
هل هو السبب في أنك خالفت وعدك؟
Cousin, I'm sorry.
ابن عمي، أنا آسف.
But don't worry.
ولكن لا تقلق.
I'll explain to my dad.
سأشرح لأبي.
Explain what?
وضح ماذا؟
I've decided to stay in Taiwan.
لقد قررت البقاء في تايوان.
Why?
لماذا؟
I fell in love with someone.
لقد وقعت في حب شخص ما.
I'll break off my engagement with Yunong
سأقطع خطوبتي مع يونونغ
and stay with him in Taiwan.
والبقاء معه في تايوان.
Cousin, I'll leave Hengfeng to you.
ابن العم، سأترك لك هنغفينغ.
You like Jiang Shaopeng?
هل تحب جيانغ شاوبنغ؟
You're off work?
هل أنت خارج العمل؟
Why are you crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
Crying?
بكاء؟
I'm not crying.
أنا لا أبكي.
You don't have to tell me,
لا داعي لأن تخبرني
but don't lie to me.
ولكن لا تكذب علي.
Sign language can't tell lies.
لغة الإشارة لا تستطيع أن تقول الأكاذيب.
I met my cousin today.
لقد قابلت ابن عمي اليوم.
I fell in love with someone.
لقد وقعت في حب شخص ما.
I'll break off my engagement with Yunong
سأقطع خطوبتي مع يونونغ
and stay with him in Taiwan.
والبقاء معه في تايوان.
Cousin, I'll leave Hengfeng to you.
ابن العم، سأترك لك هنغفينغ.
You like Jiang Shaopeng?
هل تحب جيانغ شاوبنغ؟
I shouldn't have
لا ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك
let you go in the sea back then.
دعك تذهب إلى البحر في ذلك الوقت.
Cousin.
ابن عم.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
You like your cousin very much?
هل تحب ابن عمك كثيرًا؟
He's awesome.
إنه رائع.
He's been determined to take over my family's business since childhood.
لقد كان مصمماً على تولي أعمال عائلتي منذ الطفولة.
He's different from me.
إنه مختلف عني.
When I was a child, I fell into the sea
عندما كنت طفلاً، سقطت في البحر
and almost got him drowned.
وكاد أن يغرق.
Perhaps because of that,
وربما لهذا السبب،
plus my father's wish for me to take over the family business,
بالإضافة إلى رغبة والدي في أن أتولى إدارة أعمال العائلة،
things have become awkward between us.
لقد أصبحت الأمور محرجة بيننا.
Sometimes,
أحيانا،
he's nice to me.
إنه لطيف معي.
Sometimes, he's cold.
في بعض الأحيان، يكون باردًا.
My family
عائلتي
value interests more than family bonds.
أقدر المصالح أكثر من الروابط العائلية.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
I quite like the atmosphere in your family.
أنا أحب الجو في عائلتك تمامًا.
Your parents care about you.
والديك يهتمون بك.
You care about them too.
أنت تهتم بهم أيضًا.
You can even joke with each other.
ويمكنك أيضًا المزاح مع بعضكما البعض.
It makes me feel
إنه يجعلني أشعر
warm and happy.
دافئ وسعيد.
My family
عائلتي
are also
هم أيضا
yours.
لك.
Do you know what you just said means?
هل تعلم ماذا تعني كلمة قلتها للتو؟
You're going back to America?
هل ستعود إلى أمريكا؟
If you really love Shaopeng,
إذا كنت تحب شاوبينج حقًا،
please leave him.
من فضلك اتركه.